YVES ISITE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Rwanda, Kigali City +250-791-457-023 yvesisite@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a qualified and professional web developer with four years of experience in frontend development with ReactJS and backend development with Node.js and Springboot. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Problem solving

Strong communication

Project management tools (Trello)

TECHNICAL SKILL

React.JS Front End coding

Node.js BE Coding

Springboot BE Coding

Git I Github

Computer Literacy

Node.js

EDUCATION

Upper High School (Associates Degree)

Rwanda Coding Academy

Location: Rwanda - Nyabihu

Lower High School

Groupe Scolaire Sainte Bernadette SAVE

Location: Rwanda - Gisagara

2017 - 2019

2020 - 2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend developer

GSSB SAVE

- Backend design with Node.js
- Models creation
- Database design with MongoDB

Frontend developer

GSSB SAVE

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

March, 2022 - April, 2022

March, 2022 - April, 2022

Backend developer March, 2022 - April, 2022 ATLP (Andela Technical Leadership Program) Backend design with Node.js • Models creation Database design with MongoDB Frontend developer March, 2022 - April, 2022 ATLP (Andela Technical Leadership Program) UI / UX design (Mockup design) • UI Implementation with React Integration with backend Frontend developer September, 2021 - November 2021 SparkCinema UI / UX design (Mockup design) • UI Implementation with React Integration with backend Frontend developer August, 2021 - September 2021 Groovinx

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

Frontend developer

Groovinx

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

Frontend developer

SkiDesign

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

Frontend developer

Liberypay

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

Frontend developer

Yo - events

- UI / UX design (Mockup design)
- UI Implementation with React
- Integration with backend

AWARDS / OTHER ACHIEVEMENTS

- Ideation and Prototyping Workshop Certificate
- Hackerrank Javascript Certificate
- Hackerrank CSS Certificate
- EFSET English Certificate

August, 2021 - September 2021

May, 2021 - July 2021

May, 2021 - July 2021

April, 2021 - Current

INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES

- Problem solving
- Chess
- Technology
- Travel
- Playing football
- Volleyball

PROJECTS

Yo - events

Venue booking platform (In progress)

Logistic

Company's stock inventory management (Completed)

LANGUAGES

English

EFSET Certificate

(Fluent)

French

(Medium experience)

Kiswahili

(Fluent)

Kinyarwanda

(Native speaker)

PROFILES

Github: <u>IsiteYves</u>

Twitter: <u>IsiteYves</u>